"P.S.
Good luck wherever you wind up."
(Penny:)Why didn't I put money on this?
(Penny:)Hey, that's my agent.
If I got the part,
(Penny:)it's still the second best thing
I've heard all day. Hello?
(Bernadette:)Am I a terrible person?
(Amy:)No. No, it was a mistake.
(Bernadette:)Am I a terrible person
that it crossed my mind
(Bernadette:)that she might die
and never see the card?
(Amy:)Now I think you're flirting
with the line.
(Amy:)-Good news?
-No, I didn't get it.
(Bernadette:)I'm so sorry.
(Amy:)You'll get offered something soon.
(Penny:)I kind of did. The part
in that awful horror movie
(Penny:)I passed on came back around.
(Penny:)Apparently, it's mine if I want it.
(Bernadette:)Are you gonna take it?
(Penny:)I don't know what to do.
(Amy:)Maybe you'll get hit
by a car and die.
(Amy:)LOL, right?
(Raj:)Hey. Emily, right?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Raj:)I don't know if you remember me.